ILGWU Research Department Records 5780/168
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Dress and Waist Industry, Minutes of the Grievance Board, May 26, 1913, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Dress and Waist Industry - Joint Meeting of the Grievance Board and the Wage Scale Board, 1913; Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  August 26, 1913
- ILGWU Research Department - contracts awarded by the War Department, 1942; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Contracts Awarded by the War Department, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By Unknown. Volume I Bulletins no. 1 - 38, March 25, 1942 - December29, 1942. Item is in English.
- Dress Industry - Arbitration Board, January 19, 1915, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Dress Industry - Minutes of Meetings of Grievance Board, Wage Scale Board; Conferences and Special Investigations, 1915, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
  January 11, 1915
- Dress Industry, Conference on Children's Dress Situation, 1913; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
  March 12, 1913
- Dress Industry, Grievance Board, July 1914, Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
  July 27, 1914
- Liberty Magazine, Aug. 27, 1938, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Will Dubinsky Upset Lewis in the C.I.O.?, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    By Will Irwin. August 27, 1938. Item is in English.
- ILGWU Research Department, Directory of Firms Under Contract w/ ILGWU, 1942; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Directory of Firms Under Contract with International Ladies Garment Workers Union, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union Research Department. Item is in English.
- General Industrial Advisory Council, WPA, 1938; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Confidential Bullitin no. 21, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By General Industrial Advisory Council. October 7, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Revision of Summary of Findings of General Industrial Advisory Council, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By General Industrial Advisory Council. This draft includes the findings acted upon by the Counsil, January 24 - 31, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Confidential Bulletin no. 22, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By General Industrial Advisory Council. Federal vs State-Local Control of Unemployment Reflief, October 25, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Confidential Bulletin no. 18, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By General Industrial Advisory Council. Points of General Agreement (Reached in Council Meeting of September 13, 1938) September 27, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Facts on the W.P.A. Labor Force in New York City and Other Related Material, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By General Industrial Advisory Council. May 19, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Unemploymeny Compensation, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By General Industrial Advisory Council. Confidential Bulletin no. 17 September 26, 1938/August 15, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: WPA Proposed Employment Program, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By General Industrial Advisory Council. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Facts on the WPA Labor Force in New York, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Unknown. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Basic Considerations Affecting a National Public Assistance Program, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: WPA Program Review Issued tp Member of General Industrial Advisory Council, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By General Industrial Advisory Council. June 6 - July 18, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Confidential Bulletin no. 21, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Preliminary Outline of the Report of the General Industrial Advisory Council to the Administrator Works Progress Administration, New York City on the Subject of Public Assistance Policies, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By General Industrial Advisory Council. Confidential Bulletin no. 23, November 10, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: General Industrial Advisory Council Basic Considerations Affecting A National Public Assistance Program, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Purposes of work Relief Defined, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    June 6, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Steady Improvement in Personnel, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Brehon Somervell, Administrator. June 13, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Type of Projects Limited, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Brehon Somevell. Administrator. June 20, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Finances Progressively Improve, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Brehon Somervell, Administrator. June 27, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Many Difficulties Beset Planning, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Brehon Somervell. July 5, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Prospect of Closer Cooperation, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Brehon Somervell, Administrator. July 11, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Fact Finding Council's Next Step, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Brehon Somervell, Administratoir. July 18, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Basic Concept and Definitions, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Brehon Somervell, Administrator. July 22, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Relief of Unemployment in Sweden, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Brehon Somervell, Administrator. August 1, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Unemployment Relief Plans Varied, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Brehon Somervell, Administrator. August 8, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Unemployment Insurance As a Factor in Unemployment Relief in the U.S., Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Brehon Somervell, Administrator. August 15, 1938. Item is in English.
- ILGWU Statement - In opposition to the removal of restrictions on industrial homework, July 1, 1981, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Statement of International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW) In Opposition to the Removal of Restrictions on Industrial Housework, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). July 1, 1981. Item is in English.
- ILGWU - Appendices to the submission, July 1, 1981, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Appendices to the Submission of the International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW), Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Graphic Magazine of Social Interpretation, November 1939, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Vladeck, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
    By John Herling. November 1939, Gas Masks Over Europe. Item is in English.
- The Nation, May 7, 1938, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Rise of David Dubinsky, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    By McAlister Coleman. May 7/14, 1938. Item is in English.
- GATT, Commentary, May 8, 1990, Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Commentary, Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
    May 8, 1990. Item is in English.
- Hemmets Journal, 1939; Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Swedish, 29 June 1939
  - Item 1: Amerikas bedste Fagforening, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
    By Aleko E. Lilius. June 29, 1939, May 1939. Item is in Polish.
- Hjemmets Journal, 1939; Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Danish
  - Item 1: Amerikas bedste Fagforening, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Look, January 2, 1940, Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Josef Stalin Russia's Dictator, Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
    By John Gunther. January 2, 1940. Item is in English.
- Dress Code Authority, 1933-1935, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Report on Dress Code Auithority, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    June 30, 1935. Item is in English.
- ILGWU Canada Locals, 1937-1940; Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
  English and French
  - Item 1: La Vestiaire de L'elegance, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    By Eleanor Lambert and Diane Papert. Item is in French.
  - Item 2: La Grande-Robe de L'etudiante, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    By Eleanor Lambert and Diana Callaway. Item is in French.
  - Item 3: Skier Considering Fashion Post, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    By The Gazette. Reprint from the Montreal Gazette, June 29, 1968. Item is in French.
  - Item 4: Craftsmanship Canadian Style, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    By Elizabeth Dingman. From the Toronto Telegram September 9, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Organizer, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    By Dressmakers' Union. Strike Bulletin April 30th 1937. Item is in French; English.
  - Item 6: Tailors, Finishers, Button-Sewers Join the Union!, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). May 8, 1934. Item is in Yiddish; English.
  - Item 7: Cloakmakers Join the Union!, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). May 29, 1934. Item is in Yiddish; English.
  - Item 8: Cloakmakers!!, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). Monday, May 14, 1934. Item is in Yiddish; English.
- Organizing Leaflets, Local 105, 1975; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Your Union Book: It Give You A Lift, Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
    By Local I05. Large Leaflets. Item is in English; Spanish.
- ILGWU Local 100, Knitgoods NYC, 1935-1941; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Progressive Shop Chairmen's Campaign Committee, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    February 17, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: History of the Knitgoods Workers' in the International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW), Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Program of the Progressive Knitgoods Workers, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    By Progressive Shop Chairmen's Campaign Committee of the Knitgoods Workers Union, Local 155, ILGWU. January 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Problems Facing the Knitgoods Joint Council, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    By Paul Tauber. May 1, 1939. Item is in English.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU - Misc. trades locals, NYC, 1941-1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Berdorf Goodman, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). Circular distributed November 14th, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Notice Calling Special Membership, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). Meeting of Local #38, for Thurs. November 13, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Bergdorf Goodman, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). November 10th, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Bergdorf Goodman, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). November 6th, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Bergdorf Goodman One Hour, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). October 23rd, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Equality for All Our Union Practices It!, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
    By Local 105 ILGWU. October 1961. Item is in English; Spanish.
  - Item 7: What Every Union Member Should Know, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
    By Local 62 ILGWU. Date Unknown. Item is in English.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU - New York (excluding NYC) locals, 1940-1949; Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Hear Ye! Hear Ye! Hear Ye! The Case of The People vs. C.I.O., Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
    By Utica Knitting Mills Organizing Committee of International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW) Affiliated with A.F. of L. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Kay Dunhill Workers Why Are They Getting So Kind to You Now, Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). March, 1941. Item is in English.
- ILGWU New Jersey Locals, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Attention!, Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
    By Plastic, Metal, Button & Novelty Workers Union. June 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Dressmakers of Local 145 I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: "The Union Makes It So" A Musical Narrative, Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
    By The Northeast Department International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). May 27, 1968. Item is in English.
- ILGWU Boston Locals, 1935; Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
  December 12, 1935; Italian
  - Item 1: Cloak, Skirt and Dressmakers, Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
    By Joint Board Cloak, Skirt and Dressmakers Union. December 12th 1935. Item is in Italian; English.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU Connecticut Locals, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: To All Cloak Workers Employed by the Independent Cloak Company, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: To the Workers of the Royal Wash Frock, Inc., Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). April 24, 1941. Item is in English.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU, Mass. (excluding Boston) Locals, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: "The Jacobsons Live Here", Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
    By Revelation Strike Committee. Item is in English.
- Organizing Leaflets, ILGWU Ohio Locals, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Abolish The Auction Block, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
    By Cleveland Joint Board. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Workers of the Federal Knitting Mill, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). Unknown Date. Item is in English.
- ILGWU - Cleveland, Ohio, 1930-1937; Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of Paul H. Douglas to the Board of Referees- Cleveland Women's Clothing Industry, on Employment Guarentee Plan. With Confidential Appendix on the Financial Status of the Employers in the Unionized Branch of the Cleveland Women's Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    By Paul H. Douglas. November, 1930. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Reviewer's Column, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    By sidney Yellen. January/April/June/March 1937. Item is in English.
- ILGWU - Georgia Locals, 1940; Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Underwear News, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). April 1940. Item is in English.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU - Philadelphia Locals, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
  English and Italian
  - Item 1: Strike Call! The General Strike Has Been Forced on Us!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
    By Waist and Dressmakers' Union, Local 50. Unknown Date. Item is in English; Italian.
- Organizing Leaflets, ILGWU - PA Locals, 1949-1955; Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Whole World's Eyes, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
    By B. P. Vidockler. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Facts on Wilkes, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Pennsylvania Organizer, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
    By International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). October 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Hello, Girls & Boys!......., Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
    By needlepoint. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Buttons'n'Bows, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
    By Greater Pittson Council International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGW). Friday, June 10th, 1949. Item is in English.
- Organizing Leaflets, ILGWU - Chicago Locals, 1935-1947; Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 'Custom-Made' Clothes Require Skill and Knack, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By Shirley Tucker. Reprinted from The Chicago Sun, Thursday, February 6, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Fur Workers Return Monday; Union Agrees to 2-Price Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By Ed Stanton. May 7, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Don't Sit Home and Wonder What's Happening at the Union Meeting for Tabin-Picker Workers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). November 10, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Hornell Strike Settled!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). November 3, 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Tomorrow is the Day!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). November 4, 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: "The Power Broke Down", Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). November 7, 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Mass Meeting White Goods Workers Union, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By White Goods Workers Union, Local 76. Thursday, August 30, 1934. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Cotton Good Workers Wake Up! Be Honest With Yourself and Answer These Questions:, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By White Goods Workers Union, Local 76. Pre-Strike Bulletin No. 2, Friday, February 8, 1935. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Workers in Sopkins Shops! You Are Called to an Important Meeting, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By White Goods Workers Union, Local 76. Friday, October 5th, (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: To All Sopkins Workers! Meeting, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By Needle Trades Workers' Industrial Union. Thursday, September 13, 1934. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Why the Cotton Dressmakers Should Join the Union, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By White Goods Workers Union, Local 76. June 1934. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: A Mass Meeting pf All White Goods Workers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By White Goods Workers Union, Local 76. Wednesday, June 6th, 1934. Item is in English.
- Organizing Leaflets, ILGWU - Tenn. Locals, 1937-1950; Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Garment Workers in Memphis Celebrate the Installation of Their Union, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    By Memphis Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Local No. 267. Saturday, February 13, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Nothing New Has Been Added, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Production or Bust! Have You Worked Your Way Up to the Bottom?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: You Can Have A Better Life Here is the Proof!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). August 1953. Item is in English.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU - Illinois (except Chicago) Locals, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Do You Want (Check Your Answer), Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Unknown Date. Item is in English.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU - Indiana Locals, 1940; Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
  August 19, 1940
  - Item 1: ward-Stilson Workers Meet the ILGWU, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). August 14, 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Sisters and Brothers, Workers of Pollock Bros., Inc.:, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
    By M. Bialis. February 9 to March 1 (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU - Michigan Locals, 1939; Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Vote for the ILGWU is a Vote for Higher Wages Shorter Hours Job Security, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). July 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Your Vote, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: The Won't Move Against The Law, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU - Wisconsin Locals, 1935-1944; Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Operators Come Now! To Your Section Meeting Right After Work, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). November 24, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Picnic, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
    By I.L.G.W.U. Local 188. July 21, 1935. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Milwaukee Joint Board Meets 1st Friday of Each Month, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). 1939 Calendar on Bottom. Item is in English.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU - Kansas City Locals, 1934-1948; Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Labor Institute, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By University of Kansas City and I.L.G.W.U. May 22, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Say! Did You Hear About, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU) Ed. Dept. June 26th to July 9th, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: How Old Are You?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: We Do Not Patronize the "Nelly Don" Dress, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By Joint Board Kansas City Locals Nos. 114, 115, 118, `19, 270, 274 International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: "Ye Shall Not Betray", Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By The Kansas City Joint Board International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Cutters Join the Union, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By Kansas City Garment Worker. July 1934. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: If the Employers are Members of an Association, Then Why Shouldn't the Workers be Members of the Union?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Here is the Answer to Company Unions. Read It and Then Ask Yourself, "How Come I Was Fooled Again.", Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By Dressmakers' Local 118, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Thursday, March 15, 1934. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: We Warned You! (Kansas City Workers Hear A. Plotkin Tell of Meeting.), Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By Joint Board, Cloack and Dressmakers of Kansas City, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Tuesday, May 8th (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Mass Meeting, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Thursday, August 3rd (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Cloakmakers, Cutters, Pressers Operators, Finisher-Examiners Fur Workers Read Carefully, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Hiding Behind Private Detectives!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Mass Meeting The Manufacturers Are Cutting Wages:, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Saturday, January 13 (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: What Shop Next?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). February 20th/21st (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: One-Day Institutes, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By University of Kansas City. Saturday, March 11, 1950. Item is in English.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU - St. Louis Locals, 1933; Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: All Curtain Shops 100% Union, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By Local No. 363 International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Strike At-- Forest City Manufacturing Company, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By Locals 181-182. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: To All the Workers of Weil-Kalter, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: The Strike On Forest City Manufacturing Company Declared Today, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). February 6th, 1935. Item is in English.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU - Minnesota Locals, 1937; Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: You Are a Member of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.. Why? Because-, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)